Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Lyrics and Sheet Music
  - Songbooks
    - The Harmony Heifers Songbook, undated; 1 copy; Notes: Spiral bound, probably typeset in the early 2000s; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - Loose pages from a binder, need to be cataloged, 1 copy; Notes: Sent to Harold by Janice Gelb Weiss, thick packet; genreform: Songbook (Box 11)
    - Monsters in the Night, Gallifrey Seven, undated; 1 copy; Notes: Handdrawn cover Origin: Gallifrey Seven, undated; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
    - Onward Pagan Warriors: A songbook for the past and future | Pirates, Cowboys, Spacemen, etc., 1 copy; Notes: Brown folder with loose white pages bound in Origin: Fitch, Ed; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Son of Dasfolk Filk Rock, 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover with dragons, mimograph conents, looks 1970s?; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
    - Space a Myth or Real, Gallifrey Seven, undated; 1 copy; Notes: Handdrawn cover Origin: Gallifrey Seven, undated; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
    - Ten Backwards presents the Coffee House at the End of the Universe Sing Along, Ten Backwards; 1 copy; Notes: Red cover, spiral bound, white pages Origin: Ten Backwards, undated; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
    - The Stories in the Movies, Gallifrey Seven, undated; 1 copy; Notes: Handdrawn cover Origin: Gallifrey Seven, undated; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
    - Three works together: The Book of Roddenberry, Dr. Trekwell and the Choir of Many Colors Present The Temple of Trek Revival Hymnal 2, the green edition, and an untitled third work which is comprised of songs, 3 copy; Notes: White cover with window and book, in a plastic bag, second one in a red folder (and additional lyrics in plastic bag) Origin: As Compiled by The Reverend Dr. Trekwell; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Filk Songs (beginning 1994), 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Red cover, staple bound; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - The Compleat Filker: Cherryh Pie, songs of C.J. Cherryh, 1987; 1 copy; Notes: From the collection of P. Cooke. Pink cover. unbound. Origin: Morgan's Mystique; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - Such Tunes as Killed Chao: parodies, songs, poems and rubbish, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Cover with cow. Signed by Lem. Staple bound pamphlet format Origin: Self published; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
    - Scattering Seeds on the Pomegranate Tour, Crowell, Mary, Dr.; 1 copy; Notes: Spiral bound songbook Origin: Mary Crowell Kickstarter (limited edition); genreform: Songbook (Box 7)
    - Don't Go Drinking With Hobbits, 1 copy; Notes: Signed. Glossy cover with pint of ale, square bound, ISBN 5-800065-443133; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Musical Mayhem, Bruns, P.F.; 1 copy; Notes: Green cover with lots of circles Origin: Bruns, P.F.; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
    - A New Selection of Old Scores: A Collection of Topical Songs and Filksongs especially compiled for ConStellation, the 41st Annual World Science Fiction Convention, 1983; 2 copy; Notes: Blue cover with floading space castle and hitch-hiking guitarist, by Eddie Jones, Origin: NESFA Press; genreform: Songbook (Box 13, Box 14)
      Songbook; Convention -- Worldcon; Convention -- WorldCon 41. ConStellation (1983)
    - 1998 a Lyrical Retrospective, 1 copy; Notes: Attributed to Mordewis Gaeafbran ap Llys aka Gerald L. Bliss aka Moss Bliss aka why the hell did choose such a long name, Moss?, staple bound, three hole punched Origin: Wiccan Road Publications; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - The Filkaholic Strikes Again, first edition, 2004; 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover with cat and mouse; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Songs of Filkaholic, Summer, 1989; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with cat in a beanie playing a guitar, spiral bound Origin: Filkaholic Publications; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Wallentinson, Denise
      - Phourplay and Beyond: Phoenix Philkbook, 1991; Wallentinson, Denise; Printed on orange paper. Staple bound, with illos; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - GAFilk
      - Songbook, 2014; Limited edition run, 1/32 Green cover, spiral bound, winged GAFilka fish f; genreform: Songbook (Box Box 8)
    - Vintagewealt: Volumes one and two, Master Efenwealt Wystle, the No Holds Bard; 1 copy; Notes: The Essential Oldies collection from master Efenwealt Wystle the No Holds Bard Origin: SCA or Ren Faire? Convention: SCA or Ren Faire?; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      Convention -- SCA or Ren Faire?; CD -- Commercial
  - Single Songs
    - Lyrics
      - The Rains of Castermere, George R. R. Martin; 1 copy; Notes: Includes The Dorninsh Man's Wife, and The Bear and the Maiden Fair and also mysteriously includes Ripple by the Grateful Dead Origin: George R. R. Martin; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 11)
        Song lyrics
      - I Am the Very Model of a Modern Unitarian, 1999; Raible, Christopher, Rev.; 1 copy; Notes: Printout of a song Origin: Printed May 31, 1999; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Ripping Beast TTTO Under the Gripping Beast, Baildon, Titania; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Ballad of the Green Death TTTO The Yeoman of the Guard by Gibert and Sullivan, Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: Three single sided sheets Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Dawn Vision TTTO: The Minstrel of the Dawn by Gorden Lightfoot, Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: One and a half sheets (second sheet is torn off) Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Good Morning, Timelord - The Pre-Dawn Crisis TTTO Good Morning Starshine (from HAIR), Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - The Doctor and the BBC TTTO: Charlie and the MTA (which is based on Wreck of Old '92), Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - The Timelord's Game, Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Three Cheers for the Bad Guys (Take me off in the TARDIS), Nisket, Andrew III; Eng, Cecelia; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - The Slash Character's Lament, Fitzsimons, Kate; 1 copy; Notes: 2 pages, single sided Origin: Unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Put Your Hand In the Hand of the Man From Gallifrey, Harrison, Vickie; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - The Lady Fair, 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Take Me Off In the Tardis TTTO: Take Me Out to the Ballgame, Davis, Kim; Wall, Shawn; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - Circles TTTO of Windmills by Alan Bell, Zak, Gwendolyn L, et al; 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet Origin: unknown; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 10)
      - C.I.A. parody of M.T.A. by Jacqueline Steiner and Bess Lomax Hawes, Brown, Ken; 1 copy; Notes: Song with chords written out above words Origin:; genreform: Song Lyrics (Box 8)
      - C.I.A. parody of M.T.A. by Jacqueline Steiner and Bess Lomax Hawes, Brown, Ken; 1 copy; Notes: Song with chords written out above words Origin:; genreform: Song Lyrics (Box 9)
      - ""M"" is for Magic Missile, Crowell, Mary, Dr.; 1 copy; Notes: Large M on the back with yellow sheet Origin: in-print (unknown version/edition): http://www.magnusretail.com/Mary_Crowell/lyrics/m_is_for_magic_missile.html; genreform: Song Lyrics (Box 9)
      - Rose Marshall's Ride, Jacques, Shawna; 1 copy; Notes: 2 pages Origin:; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 9)
      - Advice to Writers, Lunacon Parody Workshop; 1 copy; Notes: Handwritten on a piece of paper Origin:; genreform: Song Lyrics (Box 8)
      - Desolation, Whitker, Mike; 1 copy; Notes: Probably from the FKO Filk Hall of Fame Concert Origin:; genreform: Song lyrics (Box 9)
    - Sheet Music
      - Arise My Love/Dark Memories, 1981; McQuillin, Cynthia, 1953-2006; 1 copy; Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin: 1981; genreform: Sheet music (Box 2)
        Sheet Music
      - DNA Boogie/undentified (possibly more lyrics and an illo), McQuillin, Cynthia, 1953-2006; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); 1 copy; Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin: Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); genreform: Sheet music (Box 2)
      - Ryan's Star/Lycanthropy, McQuillin, Cynthia, 1953-2006; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); 1 copy; Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin: Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); genreform: Sheet music (Box 2)
      - Sheet Music for Forever Autumn, Osborne, Gary; Vigrass, Paul,; Music by Jeff Wayne; 2 copy; Notes: 4 pages - this is a Moody Blues song, looks this was from Mike Whitaker's set at FKO 2017; genreform: Sheet music (Box 9)
      - One Mile Closer to the Stars, 1 copy; Notes: Handwritten sheet music notation by Roberta with allusion Greg Baker; genreform: Sheet music (Box 16)
      - Solar Privateer, 1 copy; Notes: From the cover of Science News, November 21, 1981, Volume 120, #21 Origin: Cover page of Science News; genreform: Sheet Music (Box 10)
    - Home Alone, Unknown year; 1 copy; Notes: Stapled upside down; genreform: Songsheet (Box 13)
      Songsheet
    - Monster Squad, 1 copy; Notes: TTTO Bad Moon Rising, single sided sheet with lyrics and chords; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - Captains Daughter, 1 copy; Notes: Printout with staples Origin: SeananMcGuire.com; genreform: Songsheet (Box 14)
    - One Mile Closer to the Stars, 1 copy; Notes: Lyrics to One Mile Closer to the Stars; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - Grandma's Jar of Pills, 1 copy; Notes: TTTO Grandma's Featherbed, single sided.; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - The Programmer's Alphabet, 1981 and 1984; 1 copy; Notes: 2 pages single sided, with chords TTTO of Sweet Betsey From Pike; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - The Starships - lyric: Glen T. Cox, tune; Jim Little, 1979, Cox, Glen T.; Little, Jim; 1 copy; Notes: Sheet music on very damaged paper. Side two has The Title Will Follow by Bill Roper and Clif Flynt Origin: Cox, Glen T. and Little, Jim; genreform: Songsheet (Box 2)
    - Tin Soldiers - lyric: Michele Cox, based on the story by Joan D. Vinge tune: Veni Immanuel/O Come O Come Immanuel on the other side of the lyrics of The Title Will Follow, Cox, Michele; 1 copy; Notes: Sheet music on one side, lyrics on the other side for The Lyrics Will Follow Origin: Cox Michele; genreform: Songsheet (Box 2)
    - Xenofilkia #29, 1 June 1993; 1 copy; Notes: Single page photocopied onto yellow paper, with Harvester, by Leslie Fish; genreform: Songsheet (Box 15)
    - Science-Fiction Song Sheet, Unknown year; 1 copy; Notes: Reprinted from a 1940 song sheet.; genreform: Songsheet (Box 13)
    - Science-Fiction Song Sheet, Unknown year; 1 copy; Notes: Reprinted from a 1940 song sheet.; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - Be Kind, 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet; genreform: Songsheet (Box 14)
    - Lord of the Dance, 1 copy; Notes: White single sided sheet; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - Motie Engineers -- cont'd, 1 copy; Notes: White single sided sheet; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - No Filk At All, 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet with song lyrics; genreform: Songsheet (Box 14)
    - Ode to Jim's Pants, 1 copy; Notes: White single sided sheet; genreform: Songsheet (Box 16)
    - Riddles of the Sphinx, 1 copy; Notes: 2 single sided sheets; genreform: Songsheet (Box 14)
    - The Bed, 1 copy; Notes: Single sided sheet with "For Harold" written in the upper left hand corner and a new verse scrawled at the bottom. Chords are written at the top; genreform: Songsheet (Box 14)
- Zines and APAs
  - APA-Q
    - DAGON #672 probably APA-Q 583, 1 March 2016; 1 copy; White cover with print; genreform: APA (Box 11)
      APA
    - DAGON #673 APA-Q 584, 1 April 2016; 1 copy; White cover with print; genreform: APA (Box 11)
  - FAN-tastic
    - FAN-tastic, Volume #1, No. #1, 1981; DAG Design; 1 copy; Contains songs and other fannish art; genreform: Zine (Box 10)
      Zine; Songbook
    - FAN-tastic, Volume #1, No. #2, 1 March 1982; DAG Design; 2 copy; Duplicate; genreform: Zine (Box 15, Box 10)
      Zine
  - Filklore: The magazine of Filk Music and Science Fiction
    - Filklore: The magazine of Filk Music and Science Fiction, Volume #1, Issue #2, 1 November 1991; 1 copy; From the collection of Judith Hayman. Blue cover with person in period clothing with electric guitar and amp. Staple bound; genreform: Zine (Box 13)
    - Filklore: The magazine of Filk Music and Science Fiction #9, 1 August 1993; 1 copy; Light green, pamphlet style, staple bound; genreform: Zine (Box 13)
  - Filking from C to C
    - Filking from C to C: Volume 2, #2, 1 October 1997; 1 copy; From the collection of Judith Hayman. Sun mooon and stars on the cover. Originally spiral bound, now staple bound; genreform: Zine (Box 13)
    - Filking from C to C: FilKONtario 10 edition, Volume 3, #1, 1 April 2000; 1 copy; From the collection of Judith Hayman, color cover with paintings and astrolabe and excited baby on back.; genreform: Zine (Box 13)
  - Frak
    - Frak 12: A Tomorrow People Fanzine, 2 copy; Green cover with table of contents. Prose zine, non-filk stories by Janet Ellicott; genreform: Zine (Box 14, Box 8)
      Zine; Zine -- Frak; Fandom -- Tomorrow People
    - Frak - A Tomorrow People Fanzine #23, 1 copy; Green cover; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
  - Kantele
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 1, Middleton, Margaret; Flynt, Clif; 2 copies; Yellow cover with a harp being played by a stream of stars; genreform: Zine (Box 15, Box 2)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 3, Middleton, Margaret; Flynt, Clif; 1 copy; White cover with a man playing a guitar with a handkerchief over his eyes. His clothes look like armor.; genreform: Zine (Box 2, Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 6, Spring, 1980; 1 copy; White cover with spaceman with a guitar looking into the distance; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 7, Summer, 1980; 1 copy; White cover with minstrel under a tree with unicorn and butterflies; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 8, Fall, 1980; 1 copy; White cover with fighting adventurers against a background of stars; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 9, Spring/Summer, 1981; 1 copy; White cover with spacescape and guitarist and celestial person; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 10, February 1982; 1 copy; White cover with tree person with a squirrel playing a wind instrument against a background of trees; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 11, Summer, 1983; 2 copies; Yellow cover with a bipedal dinosaur in a suit with bolo tie; genreform: Zine (Box 15, Box 16)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 12, Fall, 1982; 1 copy; Blue cover with person with instrument surrounded by mythical creatures; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Kantele - A Filksing Fanzine, vol 14, Winter, 1984-5; 1 copy; Blue cover with person sitting in window with a harp. Printed by Off Centaur; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
  - Musical Chas: A Filksong Fanzine
    - Musical Chas: A Filksong Fanzine, Issue 0.5, preview edition, Spring 1980; 1 copy; White cover with Miro style abstract art; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Musical Chas: A Filksong Fanzine, Issue 3, Volume 2, Number 2, Whole Number 4, 1 August 1981; 1 copy; White cover with All That Chaz in All That Jazz font; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
  - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non (PFNEN)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #14, 13 November 1982; Philk Press; 1 copy; Green cover, with vampire and castle; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
      Zine; Zine -- Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #15, 11 December 1982; Philk Press; 1 copy; Pink cover with Santa reading a letter; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - From the Cockpit - post convention songbook of Con-Chord 5.1, 1983; 2 copies; Light blue cover with cockpit. Staple bound; genreform: Zine; genreform: Songbook (Box 14, Box 16)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #16, 22 January 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with a bard singing to a dragon; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #17, 12 February 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Blue cover, with a mechanical frog; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #18, 30 April 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Peach cover, frogs eating at tables while wearing clothes; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non #19, 14 May 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover with a man with tent in front of house; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #20, 18 June 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Green cover with frog with hermeroid cream under his arm; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #21, 23 July 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Red cover with animal theme; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #22, 13 August 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with scarecrow playing guitar; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #23, 24 September 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Blue cover with extreme excuse about where the artwork went; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #24: Official Filk Zine of the 2083 Olympics, 15 October 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Neon green cover with abstract gorilla face; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #25: Second Anniversary, 12 November 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Spaceman playing guitar on a stump to an alien; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #26: Official Filkzine of Bayfilk 2, 17 December 1983; Philk Press; 1 copy; Family of frogs in a car, driving to Bayfilk, with instruments; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #27: Offical Filkzine of Bayfilk 2, 21 January 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Pink cover with exploding clarinet frog cartoon; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #28: Offical Filkzine of Bayfilk 2, 25 February 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with faces; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #29: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 24 March 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Blue with a person playing guitar, looks like a Phil Foglio drawing, but it actually by Mel White; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #30: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 14 April 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Peach cover with frogs filking; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #31: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 19 May 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Orange cover with a unicorn rearing, nominated for best fanzine hugo!; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #32: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 23 June 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Green cover with guy with sword; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #33: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 28 July 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Red cover with man on telephone; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #34: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 11 August 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with wizard and staff; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #35: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 20 October 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Blue cover with update about losing the Hugo award; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #36: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 10 November 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; Neon green cover with a dragon and a kite; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #37: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 12 December 1984; Philk Press; 1 copy; White cover with Enterprise colliding with enormous bra; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #38: Offical Filkzine of ConChord 2, 12 January 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Light blue with man with wolf; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #39, 2 February 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Pink cover with man on stage with microphone; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #40, 30 March 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with person with lyre; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #41, 27 April 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Blue cover with furry people at a con. They may be cavemen, as there are "cave drawings".; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #42, 18 May 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover, with singing werewolf quartet; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #43, 22 June 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Light green cover with person on horseback; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #44, 27 July 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Dark green cover with person leading a horse; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #45, 17 August 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; Red cover with six legged alien walking; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #46, 21 September 1985; Philk Press; 3 copy; Neon green cover with chemist frog; genreform: Zine (Box 11, Box 2)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #47, 26 October 1985; Philk Press; 1 copy; White cover with evergreen trees at night; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - The Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non: Bayfilk III update, 1986; Willett, Paul J.; 2 copy; Features a Bayfilk 3 update and a cover caricature of Paul J. Willitt; genreform: APA (Box 2, Box 11)
    - The Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #52, 1 March 1986; Willett, Paul J.; Philk Press; 3 copies; Yellow cover with a man seranading a woman with a lute; genreform: APA (Box 2, Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #53, 1 April 1986; Philk Press; 1 copy; Light blue cover with people sleeping in the con suite; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #54, 1 May 1986; Philk Press; 1 copy; Peach cover with NASA shuttle Atlantis going up; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #55, 1 June 1986; Philk Press; 1 copy; Orange cover with person with robot; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #56: Hard system reset issue, 1 June 1989; Philk Press; 3 copy; Green cover with person with big anxious eyes and fangs. Three year hiatus; genreform: Zine (Box 11, Box 10)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #57, 1 July 1989; Philk Press; 2 copy; Red cover with picture of a brawl titled Bardic Circle; genreform: Zine (Box 11, Box 10)
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non, #58: The Still Going Issue, 1 February 1991; Philk Press; 1 copy; Yellow cover with scary Energizer Bunny; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
  - Philly Philk Phlash
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #1, July 1987; 1 copy; White cover spaceman with Concertina and drum; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #2, October, 1987, 1 copy; Purplish cover with alien reading or singing from Christmas in Arkham; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #3, January 1988, 2 copies; Yellow cover, lizard man and space man (Spaceman has "Band from Argo" on his drum.); genreform: Zine (Box 11, Box 16)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #4, Spring/Summer 1988; 1 copy; Yellow cover, three birds and pteradon in a tree; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #5, October 1988, 1 copy; Blue cover, dancing pumpkin head skeletons; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #6, Winter/Spring 1989; 2 copies; Pink cover with BEM cupid against a heart backdrop. Staple bound.; genreform: Zine (Box 11, Box 16)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #7, Spring 1989; 2 copies; Light blue cover, summer scene, with centaur and mermaids; genreform: Zine (Box 16, Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #8, ,Summer 1989; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover with cat holding smaller cat; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Philly Philk Phlash, Issue #8, Summer 1989, 1 copy; Goldenrod cover with cat holding smaller cat; genreform: Zine (Box 16)